Evil Rises.
Ginger Snaps Back: The Beginning is a horror, drama,
western film directed by Grant Harvey.
Set in 19th Century Canada, Brigitte and her sister Ginger take refuge in a
Traders' Fort which later becomes under siege by some savage werewolves.
But when one of the girls is bitten, they have no one to turn to but themselves.
Ginger Fitzgerald, played by Katharine Isabelle.
Brigitte Fitzgerald, played by Emily Perkins.
Hunter, played by Nathaniel Arcand.
James, played by JR Bourne.
Reverend Gilbert, played by Hugh Dillon.
Seamus, played by Adrien Dorval.
Ginger Snaps Back: The Beginning is a 2004 Canadian horror film and a
prequel to Ginger Snaps and Ginger Snaps 2: Unleashed.
The third and final installment in the Ginger Snaps series takes place in 19th century Canada, following the ancestors of the Fitzgerald sisters of the two
previous films: Ginger (Katharine Isabelle) and Brigitte (Emily Perkins), who are identical in all respects to their modern-day counterparts.
The film explores themes of bite, transformation, forest, sister, best friend.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.